<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nintendo on hi</title>
    <link>https://kimchiest.com/tags/nintendo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nintendo on hi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kimchiest.com/tags/nintendo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Sexual Emergency</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/emergency/</guid>
      <description>Things you can do(other than sex) during lockdown
 Buy OneWheel and ride Send me invitation on Animal Crossing  I remember same time of last year, It was lockdown stage 4 and people were horny as usual. Maybe even hornier than ever. Restriction made people crazy, nothing to do so better have sex! Guys look for sex workers even during WW2 so&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t worry too much about having blueballs, If there&amp;rsquo;s a will, there&amp;rsquo;s a way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Tricks</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/dirtytricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/dirtytricks/</guid>
      <description>Recently, strange things are happening and I hope it’s only a coincidence.
 No. 5 WeChat was blocked 3 times in 4 weeks because we apparently violated user rules. We only did what other shops do. No. 5 website was taken down from google search result today because the landing page picture was exposing too much body part, We had a naked woman showing her titties pic on our first page last year and had zero problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch, Sex Chair</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/nintendosexchair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/nintendosexchair/</guid>
      <description>Got nintendo switch for late bday present, I am not complaining but… I don’t have friends to play mariokart together ok
   Presents that i got a lot
 Powerbanks/ portable chargers Gaming stuffs   Nintendo wii Nintendo ds Nintendo switch  I understand why people give me batteries but what about nintendos, do I look like Pokémon trainer?
Last Saturday I went out 3 times to just ride OW.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
