<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on hi</title>
    <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on hi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kimchiest.com/logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>kimchiest.com</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/midjune2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/logs/midjune2021/</guid>
      <description>Ok I did it again, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand with notion anymore even though it&amp;rsquo;s simple and easy to maintain.
I want to make my blog
 fast no javescript, minimum lines of code fully functional still  Now kimchiest.com is 10 mb big and 9.6 mb are from media (picture) so it&amp;rsquo;s pretty good :D
It still has darkmode but only works when your device is set to darkmode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shiori-fujino.github.io</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/shiorifujinoio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/logs/shiorifujinoio/</guid>
      <description>Shiori-fujino.com was getting too hot. Gloriously, I got a psycho stalker too for the first time in my life. I wrote about private escort work with Celine when there was level 4 lockdown going on, also about crazy bitch ass stalker hayabi666. I also tried to write new things like interviewing Aoi.
In the meantime, my mental health was going downhill. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know that I was getting delusional. I was even locked in psychward for 15 days because of these unexplainable delusional thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shiori-fujino.com</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/shiorifujino/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/logs/shiorifujino/</guid>
      <description>I quit had a break from management position. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any more good girls, had a dull time with advertising and marketing, didn&amp;rsquo;t like new staff, and I thought it is a waste if I don&amp;rsquo;t work as a working girl when I&amp;rsquo;m still fresh.
I started my sex career at a relatively younger age. When I was Christmas at 5*(not No. 5) I was only early 20&amp;rsquo;s. As you know, the younger the better in this industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cutebutpsycho.com</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/cutebutpsycho/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/logs/cutebutpsycho/</guid>
      <description>I had to change or renew a domain after a year of having chelseastayshealthy.com. I was still healthy, spent most of my time doing yoga and I wrote about yoga a lot. I also wrote some behind stories of brothel management. Around this time, I could find good quality Korean girls and I wrote about them too. Also about the receptionist, I remember the title was like No. 5, the receptionist graveyard or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chelseastayshealthy.com</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/logs/chelseastayshealthy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/logs/chelseastayshealthy/</guid>
      <description>This was my first domain which I started in 2015 with WordPress. I think I did Brazillian Jiujitsu, weight lift, and yoga at that time, and I thought stay healthy is the way of life.
I think my first few posts were about heart broken story. I got dumped by Korean boii and cried days and nights. After a while He found my teary post about him and left some comments, people made fun of him and I felt little sorry for him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
