<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Notes</title>
    <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Record After Twenty Hours Of Sleep</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/twentyhours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/twentyhours/</guid>
      <description>I thought Invega sustenna (paliperidone injection) would last for a month, but I sleep much more than last week. Last week I thought meds finally start wearing off. I was a bit more buoyant, more motivated, but it all came back to &amp;ldquo;empty-inside&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;dead-inside&amp;rdquo; phase since yesterday. I still lactate a lot, and today I slept for almost 20 hours. I asked work to give me some more tasks, I think I need something to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surviving</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/surviving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/surviving/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s from meds or my messed-up lifestyle, my face is covered by acne. It&amp;rsquo;s depressing to look in the mirror. Things are changing in no time. Before the breakdown, I spent my days in front of a mirror or taking a selfie.
I started to eat junk food. I even had 2 hash browns in a row the other day. Plus, Domino&amp;rsquo;s puff pastry is back. It&amp;rsquo;s a shame not many people like this gourmet food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Took So Long</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/whytooksolong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/whytooksolong/</guid>
      <description>I had few goals to achieve before 2020 ends.
 Fix computers: I edited some system files (I only remember sudoer.d) from my desktop and laptop and now I can&amp;rsquo;t use it at all. I went to Apple store today, though they can&amp;rsquo;t help me either because I don&amp;rsquo;t have a proof of purchase(receipt)&amp;hellip; Get motorbike checked up: Dashboard says to get serviced since December. Make a new blog  I wanted to build a new blog from the time when I closed my previous one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medication Journal</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/medicationjournal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/medicationjournal/</guid>
      <description>My first schizo episode was July 2020, and I had to stay in the hospital for more than two weeks.
It was ok. Fun people around, interesting activities, free meals and snacks, could order uber-eats sometimes, visitors brought me a lot of sweets. The only problem was a single bed, and 90 minutes of limited internet access time.
I start my antipsychotic drug journey with Olanzapine. It was great. Although I slept 20 hours a day, I was zombie-like while awake, I stopped seeing or hearing things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Trend</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/marketingtrend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/marketingtrend/</guid>
      <description>1st Generation - walk the streets and pick up on the corner
2nd Generation - Internet
I was one of the beneficiaries of the 2nd generation sex worker industry. In the 2nd wave, consumers could share their experiences and thoughts with many more people through the magic of the internet (forums). Communicating with them through the discussion board and hanging out via social media worked great for me. Guys are always thirsty for not only nude-selfie, but also companionship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Hiring!</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/wearehiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/wearehiring/</guid>
      <description>Hi
I am nobody, I work at No.5 as management. These days I do everything. I advertise, clean offices, help other staff, deliver food for girls, write this… But I used to be a working girl too.
I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it and done it all, so not much surprises me these days. But when I first started, I used to be curious about this industry. Is it like in the movies, prostitution are run by gangsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>shiori-fujino.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>This notepad is made after many fails of other blog set-ups and many other failures in my life.
I had a blog that I used to write about sex, relationship and other personal issues. I ran for about 5 years and had to close it because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle too much attention. I started it to get attention, and I succeeded it. But it was too much for me.
Over half a year, I was locked-in psychward twice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
