<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on hi</title>
    <link>https://kimchiest.com/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on hi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kimchiest.com/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Mongol Town</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/mongol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/mongol/</guid>
      <description>I just finished bootcamp in a Mongolian town.
   Have you ever seen Mongol Shop
   Mongol foods (and kimchi?)
   Mongol desserts
   Mongol&amp;hellip; fried dough?
   Mongol coffee (?)
   Mongol bags
   My choice: Mongol cake that is made of cream cheese, condensed milk, and possibly&amp;hellip; oreo powder?
As I mentioned in the previous post, I wasn’t Celine’s exclusive booker this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Hiring!</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/hiring/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
I am currently working at a brothel as a management. I do everything. I advertise, clean offices, help other staff, deliver food for girls, take picture of girls, write this… But I used to be a working girl, service provider too.
I’ve seen it and done it all, so not much surprises me these days. But when I first started, I used to be curious about this industry. Is it like in the movies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>r/cringetopia</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/cringe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/cringe/</guid>
      <description>Hi, having busy days while making darker, red-er rooms.
   using marker and clear sticky tape
   using post-it
   and it&amp;rsquo;s like this!
   but&amp;hellip; money can do better job. (phillips hue ricebowl series)
   paying home loan&amp;hellip; (never ends)   taking picture of dead animal   my favourite ni-hao tee
I can&amp;rsquo;t wait til i can talk about this pandemic secret gentlemen&amp;rsquo;s society!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirror Mirror On The Wall</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/mirror/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking a lot of girls&#39; pictures and I have reached a conclusion that selfies can be more attractive than photos that were taken by another person, when it comes to sex worker&amp;rsquo;s profile pictures.
Of course, hiring a professional with a proper setting is different. Let&amp;rsquo;s say we use the same iPhone X as our only equipment.
   This, can&amp;rsquo;t be any worse. Apart from anything (cloth, shoes, angle, lighting etc) She just looks so awkward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sexual Emergency</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/emergency/</guid>
      <description>Things you can do(other than sex) during lockdown
Buy OneWheel and ride Send me an invitation on Animal Crossing I remember same time of last year, It was lockdown stage 4 though people were horny as usual. Maybe even hornier than ever. Restriction made people crazy, nothing to do so better have sex! Guys looked for sex workers even during WW2 so… don’t worry too much about having blueballs, If there’s a will, there’s a way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Tricks</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/dirtytricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/dirtytricks/</guid>
      <description>Recently, strange things are happening and I hope it’s only a coincidence.
 No. 5 WeChat was blocked 3 times in 4 weeks because we apparently violated user rules. We only did what other shops do. No. 5 website was taken down from google search result today because the landing page picture was exposing too much body part, We had a naked woman showing her titties pic on our first page last year and had zero problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhodes</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/rhodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/rhodes/</guid>
      <description>Hello diabetes&amp;hellip; Machi machi Rhodes finally opened last week.
   Bengong is still my number one for brown sugar pearl milk tea though I like machi machi&amp;rsquo;s panna cotta series too. I waited 45 minutes to get 2 bottles of it when machi just opened at Sydney city, I was displeased at first but I thought it&amp;rsquo;s worth to wait after I had a sip. lol
   Not only Bengong&amp;rsquo;s and Machi-machi, there are some good eats in Rhodes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/ugly/</guid>
      <description>I want to punch people in their jaw sometimes, especially those cowards, keyboard warriors.
I was doing my work routine, checking reviews, update website and so on and I found out a customer calls out a working girl ugly only because she&amp;rsquo;s not his cup of tea whereas other people still think She&amp;rsquo;s cutiepie. I mean&amp;hellip; is it ok to describe a human as ugly?
Some people might think it&amp;rsquo;s ok because working girls are there to be judged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Trend</title>
      <link>https://kimchiest.com/posts/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kimchiest.com/posts/marketing/</guid>
      <description>Sex worker market 1st Generation - Walk the streets and pick up on the corner
2nd Generation - Internet
I was one of the beneficiaries of the 2nd generation sex worker industry. In the 2nd wave, consumers could share their experiences and thoughts with many more people through the magic of the internet (forums). Communicating with them through the discussion board and hanging out via social media worked great for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
